mohegansun.com 2019-01-14

# Privacy Policy | Mohegan Sun

  *  SUN WINE & FOOD FEST 
  * GAMING & PROMOS
    * Gaming
      * Gaming
      * Overview
      * Slots
      * Table Games
      * Poker
      * Race Book
      * Responsible Gaming
      * Casino Credit
      * Tax Forms
    *  Current Promos 
      * Current Promos
    *  Play Online 
      * Play Online
    * Momentum
      * Momentum
      * Momentum Overview
      * Core
      * Ignite
      * Leap
      * Ascend
      * Soar
      * Play+
      * Momentum Travel Associates
      * Momentum Partnerships
    * Casinos
      * Casinos
      * Casino of the Earth
      * Casino of the Sky
      * Casino of the Wind
  * ENTERTAINMENT
    *  Event Calendar 
      * Event Calendar
    * Mohegan Sun Arena
      * Mohegan Sun Arena
      * About the Arena
      * Calendar
      * Arena Suites
      * Arena Policies
    * Wolf Den
      * Wolf Den
      * About the Wolf Den
      * Calendar
    * Comix Mohegan Sun
      * Comix Mohegan Sun
      * About Comix Mohegan Sun
    * Nightlife
      * Nightlife
      * Nightlife Venues
      * Calendar
      * Plan Your Event
    * Tastings & Festivals
      * Tastings & Festivals
      * Sun Wine & Food Fest
      * Sun Whiskey Union
      * Sun BBQ Fest
      * Sun Tequila Tasting
      * Cigar Social
      * New England Food Truck Festival
      * Sun BrewFest
    *  Convention & Expo Events 
      * Convention & Expo Events
    *  Connecticut Sun 
      * Connecticut Sun
    *  New England Black Wolves 
      * New England Black Wolves
    *  Signature Events 
      * Signature Events
    *  Back Of House 
      * Back Of House
    *  Kids Quest & Cyber Quest 
      * Kids Quest & Cyber Quest
    *  Supercharged 
      * Supercharged
  * DINE & SHOP
    * Dining
      * Dining
      * All Restaurants
      * Dining Specials
      * Casual Dining
      * Fine Dining
      * Bars & Nightclubs
      * Reservations
    * Shopping
      * Shopping
      * All Shops
      * Shopping Specials
      * Apparel
      * Jewelry
      * Electronics
    *  Mohegan Sun Gift Cards 
      * Mohegan Sun Gift Cards
  * HOTEL, SPA & GOLF
    *  Book A Stay 
      * Book A Stay
    * Hotel Overview
      * Hotel Overview
      * Overview
      * Sky Tower
      * Earth Tower
      * Aspire & Thirty Three
      * Special Packages
      * Amenities
      * Plan An Event
      * Area Hotels
      * Getting Here
    *  Spas at Mohegan Sun 
      * Spas at Mohegan Sun
      * Mohegan Sun Golf Club
  *  MEETINGS 
  * ABOUT US
    *  About Mohegan Sun 
      * About Mohegan Sun
    *  Getting Here 
      * Getting Here
    *  Contact Us 
      * Contact Us
    *  FAQs 
      * FAQs
    *  ADA Guest Services 
      * ADA Guest Services
    *  Careers 
      * Careers
  * LOCATIONS
      * ilani (WA)
      * Mohegan Sun Pocono (PA)
      * Resorts Casino Hotel (NJ)
  *  SIGN UP & SAVE 
  * MY MOHEGAN SUN
    *  Overview 
    *  Book A Visit 
    *  My Promos and Offers 
    *  My Reward Points 
    *  My Calendar 
    *  My Reservations 
    * My Account Info
      * My Account Info
      * Update Account
      * Tax Forms
      * Casino Credit

This Privacy Policy explains what information is collected via the Mohegan Sun website located at mohegansun.com, why the information is collected and how it is used. Mohegan Sun does not share or sell your personal information to anyone. Mohegan Sun does not participate in any format of SPAM and will not send any unsolicited emails.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE

The information collected online is used for email broadcasts utilizing tailored information upon the request of a visitor. Information received such as name, email address, home address and data collected regarding areas of interest is stored in a database. The database is available for Mohegan Sun's usage only and is not shared with anyone. None of the information collected is sold or shared with any third party and is available only to specific Marketing Managers at Mohegan Sun. Anyone receiving email updates from Mohegan Sun that wish to be removed should immediately click on the "unsubscribe" link which is included in every email correspondence that is transmitted from Mohegan Sun.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED AT MOHEGAN SUN

In addition to the information collected online, patrons may sign up to become a [Momentum](https://mohegansun.com/momentum.html) ** ** member upon visiting Mohegan Sun. All personal information collected at any Player's Club booth including name, address, phone number and email address is placed in a database that is not shared or sold with any third party.

### MANAGEMENT OF USER INFORMATION

Certain information, such as address or email address, can be updated or corrected simply by calling Customer Service at 1.888.777.7920.

### SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN

This site is not intended for children. Children may use this site only with the direct supervision of their parent or legal guardian. We do not attempt to collect any data or personal information from children. Any parents or guardians who are aware of children submitting information should notify us at once of the specific information so that we may remove them from any mailing lists. All recipients of any online promotions must be 21 years of age or older. Age is verified upon contact of the specified winner.

### IF YOU HAVE A QUESTION

If you have a question regarding any of the above information, please contact us at the following email address and we will be happy to get back to you.

Email: [information@mohegansun.com](mailto:information@mohegansun.com)

You may also contact us by mail using the address below:

**1 Mohegan Sun Boulevard  
Uncasville, CT 06382**

**For General Information:** 1.888.226.7711  
**For Hotel Reservations:** 1.888.777.7922
